https://www.texascares.org/privacy

Texas CARES Privacy Policy
We will invite you to volunteer, foster or donate. Texas CARES receives no local, state or federal tax support, nor any United Way funding. We are able to provide our programs and services thanks to the generosity of individuals, corporations and foundations. Because we rely on donations, we will offer you the opportunity to contribute to our mission of caring for our cats whenever you voluntarily submit your name, postal and/or e-mail address or phone numbers. Examples of voluntarily submitting information include (but are not limited to) making a donation and applying to adopt, volunteer or foster.
How we will use your information:
We will use your name, address, email address and/or phone number in order to:
Send information to you, such as newsletters regarding the activities of Texas CARES
Request donations of you and to acknowledge donations made by you in honor of others
Keep a record of your donations made to the organization in accordance with established accounting procedures. Personal information is stored in a secure database which is accessible only to authorized personnel of Texas CARES. Name and address information is released to third-party vendors such as mail houses preparing letters on behalf of Texas CARES; this information is destroyed by these vendors after use.
We never share or sell your personal information
Texas CARES will not sell, trade or share donors’ personal information with anyone else, nor send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations. We will only share donor information once the donor has given us specific permission.
What are cookies?
Non-personal information and data may be automatically collected when you visit our web site through the use of “cookies”. Cookies are small text files a website uses to “recognize” repeat visitors, facilitate your access to and throughout our site, allow our site to track usage behavior and compile data that will allow for content improvements. In other words, Texas CARES uses cookie technology to obtain non-personal information from you in order to facilitate your visit and improve your experience within our site. Cookies are not programs that come onto your system or damage your files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to you; these numbers have no meaning outside of our site. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a procedure in most browsers which allows you to deny the cookie feature.
Online Pay Adoption Fee DonationTexas CARES Adoption Center in PetSmart Prosper, TXMonday7:00 AM - 9:00 PMTuesday7:00 AM - 9:00 PMWednesday7:00 AM - 9:00 PMThursday7:00 AM - 9:00 PMFriday7:00 AM - 9:00 PMSaturday7:00 AM - 9:00 PMSunday7:00 AM - 6:00 PM1001 South Preston Rd
Prosper, Texas 75078
(972) 356-5609
Opens Feb 26, 2018
Texas CARES Adoptions inside Cat Connection Monday8:00 AM - 6:00 PMTuesday8:00 AM - 6:00 PMWednesday8:00 AM - 6:00 PMThursday8:00 AM - 6:00 PMFriday8:00 AM - 6:00 PMSaturday8:00 AM - 5:00 PMSundayCLOSED14233 Inwood Road
Dallas, TX, 75244
Earthwise Pet FriscoMonday10AM-5PMTuesday10AM-5PMWednesday10AM-5PMThursday10AM-5PMFriday10AM-5PMSaturday9AM-5PMSundayCLOSED252 W. Stonebrook Pkwy Suite 650
Frisco, TX 75036
972-301-8277
Stay updated on Texas CARESSubscribe to our newsletter
Name:
Donate Cat & Cleaning Supplies
Pet Food Online with 20% off + Free Shipping!
Boon Supply Fundraiser (Ends Dec 31. 2020_
Thru Dec 31, 2020 - Who needs some cute supplies for their home office? Or maybe a new bag to take picnic supplies to the park? Or a cute emoji pancake pan? If you do - or you know someone who does - consider shopping online at Boon Supply! 40% of every purchase goes to Texas CARES!
Etsy Fundraiser
We’re excited to partner with Steph’s Crafts Bits! Her jewelry is super cute and 20% of every sale goes to Texas CARES. Be sure to write “Texas CARES” in the NOTES section when you check out! Thank you for your support!
Texas CARES Privacy Policy
About
Home
Contact Us
Our Cats
Adoption Application
Donate
Resources
